{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Pre-Fabricated Fireplace Installers","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/40247/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40247,"taskName":"Pre-Fabricated Fireplace Unit - Install","taskDescription":"Install a Pre-Fabricated Fireplace Unit","xmTaskDescriptor":"Pre-Fabricated Fireplace Installers","matchable":false,"profileable":false,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":79,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Fireplace stove wood ventless free","textMessagingName":"Install Gas Fireplace","rolloverLongDesc":"Install or replace pellet stoves, wood stoves, fireplaces units \u0026 gas log sets. Can handle both natural gas \u0026 propane hook ups.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes gas, wood \u0026 pellet burning units.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install a Pre-Fabricated Fireplace Unit.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Pre-Fabricated Fireplace Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Prefab Fireplace Builders","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":31,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":4,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Pre-Fabricated Fireplace Unit Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Pre-Fabricated Fireplace Unit - Install","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Pre-Fabricated Fireplace Project","urlName":"Pre-Fabricated-Fireplace-Unit-Install","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Pre-Fabricated Fireplace Installers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Fireplace,stove,wood,ventless,vent,stone,outdoor,log,gas,mantel,firepalce,faux,fireplaces,electric,corner,prefabricated,Pre-Fabricated,Unit,chimney,Replacement, inserts","emcCategoryOid":-12031,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":554,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40247/":{"taskOID":40247,"originalTaskOID":40247,"setID":554,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":6770,"questionDisplayText":"Will your fireplace use natural gas?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Will your fireplace use natural gas?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502285,"questionDisplayText":"Fireplace install","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes this fireplace install?","shortQuestionText":"What best describes this fireplace install?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3222,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Inserting into an existing masonry fireplace","answerDisplayText":"Inserting into an existing masonry fireplace","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3280,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Installed into a newly framed opening","answerDisplayText":"Installed into a newly framed opening","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4700,"questionDisplayText":"Type of insert","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"In what type of gas fireplace insert are you interested?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4038,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Natural vent","answerDisplayText":"Natural vent","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1930,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Direct vent","answerDisplayText":"Direct vent","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6613,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Unvented (vent free)","answerDisplayText":"Unvented (vent free)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7061,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Wood burning type","answerDisplayText":"Wood burning type","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4455,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other (describe in additonal details box below)","answerDisplayText":"Other (describe in additonal details box below)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4704,"questionDisplayText":"Features wanted","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What features most interest you? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6197,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Supplemental heating","answerDisplayText":"Supplemental heating","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2472,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Fireplace ambience","answerDisplayText":"Fireplace ambience","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2384,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Fan","answerDisplayText":"Fan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5143,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Remote control","answerDisplayText":"Remote control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6763,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Wall switch","answerDisplayText":"Wall switch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6767,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Wall-mounted thermostat","answerDisplayText":"Wall-mounted thermostat","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":6770,"questionDisplayText":"Will your fireplace use natural gas?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Will your fireplace use natural gas?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502285,"questionDisplayText":"Fireplace install","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes this fireplace install?","shortQuestionText":"What best describes this fireplace install?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3222,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Inserting into an existing masonry fireplace","answerDisplayText":"Inserting into an existing masonry fireplace","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3280,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Installed into a newly framed opening","answerDisplayText":"Installed into a newly framed opening","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3222,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Inserting into an existing masonry fireplace","answerDisplayText":"Inserting into an existing masonry fireplace","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3280,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Installed into a newly framed opening","answerDisplayText":"Installed into a newly framed opening","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4700,"questionDisplayText":"Type of insert","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"In what type of gas fireplace insert are you interested?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4038,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Natural vent","answerDisplayText":"Natural vent","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1930,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Direct vent","answerDisplayText":"Direct vent","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6613,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Unvented (vent free)","answerDisplayText":"Unvented (vent free)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7061,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Wood burning type","answerDisplayText":"Wood burning type","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4455,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other (describe in additonal details box below)","answerDisplayText":"Other (describe in additonal details box below)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4038,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Natural vent","answerDisplayText":"Natural vent","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1930,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Direct vent","answerDisplayText":"Direct vent","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6613,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Unvented (vent free)","answerDisplayText":"Unvented (vent free)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7061,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Wood burning type","answerDisplayText":"Wood burning type","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4455,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other (describe in additonal details box below)","answerDisplayText":"Other (describe in additonal details box below)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4704,"questionDisplayText":"Features wanted","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What features most interest you? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6197,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Supplemental heating","answerDisplayText":"Supplemental heating","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2472,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Fireplace ambience","answerDisplayText":"Fireplace ambience","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2384,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Fan","answerDisplayText":"Fan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5143,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Remote control","answerDisplayText":"Remote control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6763,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Wall switch","answerDisplayText":"Wall switch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6767,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Wall-mounted thermostat","answerDisplayText":"Wall-mounted thermostat","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6197,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Supplemental heating","answerDisplayText":"Supplemental heating","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2472,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Fireplace ambience","answerDisplayText":"Fireplace ambience","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2384,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Fan","answerDisplayText":"Fan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5143,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Remote control","answerDisplayText":"Remote control","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6763,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Wall switch","answerDisplayText":"Wall switch","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6767,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Wall-mounted thermostat","answerDisplayText":"Wall-mounted thermostat","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"isCookielessUser":true}